

### **PROFILE**

5 years of experience in analysis, design development and implementation of asp.net web application. Experienced in SQL server 2008 to 2017 with complex query and stored procedure. Worked with Asp.Net, .Net Core, Entity Framework, Angular Js, Angular, Vue Js, Crystal Report, RDLC Report, Make PDF, iTextSharp. Also Familiar with Azure, AWS, Github and Docker.

### CONTACT

PHONE: +880 1740 966 056

WEBSITE:

www.kaynat.info

**EMAIL:** 

rahee.aiub@gmail.com

### **PROJECTS**

- Payroll Management
- Hotel Management
- MIS Reporting
- HR Management
- Point of Sale
- Inventory Management
- Gold Management
- Micro Credit
- Sales Data Control
- Tobacco Management

# GOLAM SARWAR-E-KAYNAT

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Mediasoft Data Systems Limited [Senior Software Engineer]

Feb 2020 - Present

Developing Web based and windows application with asp.net and MS SQL Server.

## A to Z Computer Service [Jr. Software Engineer]

Oct 2017 - Feb 2020

Developed Payroll, HR, Gold Management and Micro Credit Union ERP Software.

## Paronsoft Solutions Ltd. [Jr. Software Engineer]

Dec 2016 - Sept 2017

Developed projects with visual basic, WCF, WPF and asp.net MVC.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Master of Business Administration**

Department of MIS (Management Information System)

#### **University of Dhaka**

Jan 2018 - Dec 2021

CGPA: 3.89

### Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Engineering

American International University-Bangladesh

May 2013 - Dec 2016

CGPA: 3.70

# **SKILLS**

